<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andryo Marzuki</title>
    <link>https://marzukia.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andryo Marzuki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2020, Andryo Marzuki</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marzukia.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Web API JWT Implementation</title>
      <link>https://marzukia.github.io/post/aspnet-jwt-webapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marzukia.github.io/post/aspnet-jwt-webapi/</guid>
      <description>Sir, can I see your ID? I&amp;rsquo;ve recently made the jump from using Django to ASP.NET Core as my primary choice when developing web applications. This was initially due to me branching into using C# for things like Unity, and later realizing how much enjoyable it was to use ASP.NET Core over Django.
As I mostly use ReactJS for my application frontends, I did not need the &amp;lsquo;Razor&amp;rsquo; pages integrated in ASP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 32 and GPU Passthrough (VFIO)</title>
      <link>https://marzukia.github.io/post/fedora32-vfio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marzukia.github.io/post/fedora32-vfio/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;What? I&amp;rsquo;ve used Fedora 32 as my main OS for about two years. Overall, it has been a very pleasant experience and has made things such as developing much easier than it would&amp;rsquo;ve been on Windows.
However&amp;hellip; gaming on Linux is frankly a pain in the ass. No matter the state of Vulkan, Proton, Wine, etc, you&amp;rsquo;ll always find Windows games which will flat out not work. More recently, I found that Escape From Tarkov did not work at all on Linux due to Easy Anticheat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://marzukia.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marzukia.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Andryo Marzuki  My name is Andryo Marzuki, I live in Auckland, New Zealand.
I develop applications which aim to commercialise or utilise data in innovative ways.
 Technical  C#, ASP.NET, Python, Django, TypeScript, ReactJS, Tensorflow, scikit-learn, PostgreSQL, Teradata, SQLite, ArcGIS, QGIS, PostGIS, GDAL, Tableau, Power BI
 Experience  Insights Manager, ANZ Bank New Zealand Limited (2018 - Present)
Director, Rentgo New Zealand Limited (2018 - 2020)
Associate, ANZ Bank New Zealand Limited (2016 - 2018)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>