<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>COVID-19 on Andryo Marzuki - Net Zero Productivity by 2050</title>
    <link>https://mrzk.io/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in COVID-19 on Andryo Marzuki - Net Zero Productivity by 2050</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mrzk.io/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did COVID-19 Help Trump Win In The 2024 Elections? Probably.</title>
      <link>https://mrzk.io/posts/did-covid19-make-trump-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mrzk.io/posts/did-covid19-make-trump-president/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a non-American observing America’s enthusiastic self-destructing, I find it utterly baffling that a man like Donald Trump could secure a second term. Over half the nation saw the individual who somehow achieved the rare feat of bankrupting not one but two casinos, which are famously designed to print money, as the best choice to lead the country. There&amp;rsquo;s definitely something wrong with America right?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinations Matter (aka Why Anti-Vaxxers Should Really Reconsider)</title>
      <link>https://mrzk.io/posts/vaccinations-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mrzk.io/posts/vaccinations-matter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Few things frustrate me more than seeing anti-lockdown protestors, anti-vaxxers, or those who believe that vaccines somehow infringe upon their personal freedoms. The value of vaccination should be self-evident to anyone with even a shred of common sense.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deeper Into New Zealand&#39;s Official Recession</title>
      <link>https://mrzk.io/posts/nz-negative-growth-unbiased-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mrzk.io/posts/nz-negative-growth-unbiased-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New Zealand has officially entered into a recession after 11 years following two consecutive periods of negative GDP growth. This last time New Zealand was in a recession was in 2008 due to the global financial crisis. Given the current circumstances, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that this has occurred.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Has New Zealand Handled COVID-19?</title>
      <link>https://mrzk.io/posts/nz-usa-covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mrzk.io/posts/nz-usa-covid19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of March, I made the unfortunate decision of investing into two exchange-traded funds (ETFs) which were SmartShare&amp;rsquo;s FNZ (NZ Top 50) and USF (Fortune 500). It was unfortunate because the world decided to set itself on fire due to the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
